Held captive for 7 years. Her story of courage is timeless.
Girl in the Box is a drama, tv movie film directed by Stephen Kemp.
The true story of 20-year-old Colleen Stan, a hitchhiking woman abducted by a young couple and held captive
for seven years, during which time she's tortured and forced to live as a slave to her captors.
Colleen Stan, played by Addison Timlin.
Cameron Hooker, played by Zane Holtz.
Janice Hooker, played by Zelda Williams.
Jack, played by Matt Cooke.
Angel, played by Shileen Paton.
Amber, played by Vivian Wright.
The Girl on the Train is a 2016 American psychological thriller film directed by Tate Taylor and written by Erin
Cressida Wilson, based on the popular 2015 debut novel of the same name by British author Paula Hawkins.
The film stars Emily Blunt, Rebecca Ferguson, Haley Bennett, Justin Theroux,
Luke Evans, Allison Janney, Édgar Ramírez, and Lisa Kudrow.
The film follows an alcoholic divorcée who becomes
involved in a missing person investigation.
Principal photography began on November 4, 2015, in New York City.
Produced by Marc Platt and DreamWorks Pictures, The Girl on the Train was the first film produced by DreamWorks Pictures to return to be distributed by Universal Pictures as part of
DreamWorks' new distribution deal via their new parent company Amblin Partners, following the end of their distribution deal with Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures earlier that year.
The Girl on the Train premiered in London on September 20, 2016, before it was
theatrically released in the United States on October 7, 2016.
The film was a box office success, grossing $173 million worldwide.
It received mixed reviews from critics, though Blunt received lead actress nominations at
the 23rd Screen Actors Guild Awards and the 70th British Academy Film Awards.
A Hindi remake was released in 2021, with Bollywood
actress Parineeti Chopra in the starring role.
The tone is emotional.